and I want to just thank you all for
joining today our one month celebration
of the most historic opening to a
presidency in American history no
president comes close to what Donald
Trump has achieved over just the last 30
days he has packed eight years of
transformative action restoring this
nation restoring our laws restoring
fairness restoring Economic Opportunity
restoring National Security in just one
month no in this country's ever seen
anything like it and when you look at
the
consequentiality and the significance in
the transformative nature of the actions
he's taking it truly defies description
for example in just one area this nation
has been plagued and crippled by illegal
discrimination diversity equity and
inclusion policies it strangled our
economy it has undermined Public Safety
it has made every aspect of life more
difficult more painful and less safe he
has ended
all Dei across the federal government he
has terminated all federal workers
involved in promulgating these unlawful
policies he has ended diversity equity
and inclusion in all federal Contracting
he has restored Merit as the Cornerstone
of all federal policy rest stored the
full Fair impartial enforcement of our
federal civil rights laws for the first
time in generations and he has cracked
down on individuals across this
government and non profets who have
engaged in illegal racial discrimination
against the American people this
includes making clear to every
educational institution in this country
that ending diversity equity and
inclusion ending unlawful race
discrimination is a precondition of
receiving federal funds he has also
saved women's sports by ending the
participation of men in women's sports
he has ended radical gender ideology
across the entire federal government and
he's pressured the private sector to
also end and combat radical gender
ideology he's reestablished the
scientific and biological truth that
there are only two sexes in this country
male and female that those are
biologically based determinations they
are not based and can never be based on
gender identity that includes rooting
out of the Department of Defense all Dei
policies all critical race Theory all
gender Madness and once again having a
military that is focused solely and
exclusively on readiness preparedness
and lethality as I'm sure Kevin will
talk about more of course he has
undertaken a historic cost cutting
effort across the federal government
launching the first ever Department of
government efficiency uncovering
corruption on a scale that we never
thought imaginable terminating every
single federal worker that we are that
we have found to be engaged in the
corruption and theft and the waste of
taxpayer dollars and already saving $50
billion in a single year which over a
10-year period would be5 100
billion just think about how vast and
enormous that sum is of course as you
all know he is renamed the Gulf of
Mexico to his correct and proper name
the Gulf of America he is renamed Mount
Denali into Mount McKinley part of a
historic effort to restore patriotism
and national pride all across this land
he has ended the weaponization of the
federal government restored the
Department of Justice to its true
mission of combating threats to this
nation and keeping the American people
safe
he has ended all federal censorship of
free speech this has been one of the
greatest crises that has plagued this
nation years and years and years the
federal government violating the First
Amendment to take away Americans right
of free speech president Trump has ended
that and he has demanded that all
federal workers all law enforcement
cease any effort to intimidate the
rights of Americans or to police their
speech he has also restored the death
penalty of the Department of Justice
including for illegal aliens who commit
murder including for those who murder
cops and including for all of those who
threaten Americans with heinous acts of
violence the death penalty is back Law
and Order is back the streets are being
made safe once again on the public
health front he has launched the
nation's first ever commission the Maha
commission make America healthy again
following the historic confirmation of
RFK Jr to finally cover the true root
causes of the Public Health crisis in
this country the childhood disease
epidemic in this country the spiraling
rates of pediatric cancer and
devastating childhood sickness he has
finally created a situation where the
federal he Health agencies in this
country will be focused on preventing
disease on keeping children from getting
sick in the first place not sending them
to a lifetime in and out of hospitals
suffering needlessly when we can find
ways to prevent this epidemic of illness
then of course on homeland security
today it is officially the law of the
land at the conclusion of the
Congressional notification process that
six Mexican cartels and two
transnational gangs Trend de Raga or TDA
and MS-13 so eight organizations in
total are now formally designated as
foreign terrorist organizations which
means that every single member of those
organiz ations who operates on us soil
is now as a legal matter a terrorist and
they will be treated as terrorists this
is a sea change in US policy and this
means the Department of Justice and the
Department of Homeland Security along
with the rest of us law enforcement and
the Department of Defense are now
operating in a legal reality where these
cartels are recognized as terrorists and
there will be a whole of government
effort to remove these terrorists from
our soil and to degrade their ability to
threaten or undermine any American
Security or sovereignty interest border
crossings since the day he took office
are down
95% I think it's almost impossible to
even describe the scale and scope of
that achievement president Trump within
days of taking office cut border
crossings
95% and those few who have dared to
cross are being either prosecuted or
deported they're either facing
significant jail time for trafficking
smuggling harboring aiding impeding or
they're being immediately removed from
our soil either way at the end of the
process they are going home he's
reimplemented remain in Mexico and he
has obtained historic cooperation from
foreign countries All Around the World
in accepting their Deportes back and he
has used the United States military to
fully seal the southern border with a
historic deployment of both active duty
and National Guard troops resumed the
building of infrastructure he has opened
up Guantanamo Bay and he's using
military aircraft to carry out
deportations all across this country and
ice is joining with ATF DEA and FBI to
carry out the largest deportation
operation in American history the
criminals are going home the border is
sealed shut America is safe Sovereign
proud and free we are a nation that
everyone in the world understands all
across this planet you do not come here
illegally you will not not get in you
will go to jail you will go home you
will not succeed this is the biggest and
most successful change in any area of
law enforcement that this nation has
ever seen and he did it in under one
month thank you